《絕命律師》前情提要
Previously on "Better Call Saul."
跟我說說電流的事兒
Tell me about the electricity.
我知道這聽起來很荒謬  但這是真的
I know how it sounds, but it's real.
我要去接那個司機
I'm picking up that driver,
如果他認出了你  那可不好
and if he knows you, that's bad.
警察沒讓上報紙嗎
The cops keeping it out of the papers?
你想讓警察去抓赫克托
You wanted to put the cops onto Hector?
他完全忘了你
He forgot all about you.
我可沒忘記他
I haven't forgotten him.
亞利桑那州斯科茨代爾羅塞拉路1216號
1216 Rosella Drive, Scottsdale, Arizona.
這可不是犯錯
This was no mistake.
他陷害了我
He sabotaged me.
-記得我嗎  -答案是不記得
- Remember me? - The answer is no.
我知道他來過
I know he was here!
我知道他都干了什么
I know what he did!
布雷迪神父在小教堂
Father Brady's in the chapel.
想叫他來的話就按呼叫按鈕
Just push the call-button if you want to see him.
你上一次吃東西是什么時候
When was the last time you ate?
什么
What?
吃的  你最近吃東西了嗎
Food. Have you eaten anything lately?
我沒事
I'm fine.
來吧  查克  我們去諾維家吃點東西
Come on, Chuck. Let's go over to Novi's
活動活動  透下氣  吃點三明治
and strech our legs, get some air, couple of hoagies.
你這個時候想吃三明治
You wanna get a sandwich now?
想想而已
Just a thought.
好吧
Alright.
你記不記得那次我不小心邀請了
Remember that time I accidentally invited
凱茜和謝麗爾參加媽媽的驚喜派對
Kathy and Cheryl to Mom's surprise party?
跳舞時有點尷尬
It was kind of tricky out on the dance floor.
那晚真有意思
It was a fun night.
我只記得全家人給你收拾爛攤子
I just remember the whole family cleaning up after you,
媽媽離開自己的生日派對
and Mom leaving her own birthday party
開車送其中一個人回家
drive one of them off.
說真的  查克  我們得吃東西
Seriously, Chuck, we gotta eat.
聽著
It -- look.
讓媽媽一個人待幾分鐘沒問題的
Mom'll be okay for a few minutes.
都三天了  還可能再持續三天
It's been three days. It could be three more.
好嗎
Okay?
走吧  哥們
Let's go, buddy.
吉米  你想吃東西就去吃吧
Jimmy, you want to eat, go eat.
我給你帶回來點什么
I'll bring you something --
烤牛肉  不加番茄  意式配菜
um, roast beef, no tomato, Italian on the side.
好嗎
All right?
好的  馬上回來
'Kay. Be right back.
媽
Mom?
吉米
Jimmy.
不  媽  是我  查克
No, Mom, it's me -- Chuck.
吉米
Jimmy.
不  媽  我是
No, Mom, it's m--
就這樣了
So this is it, then?
我很遺憾
I'm sorry.
她簽過不搶救預囑
She has that DNR.
你弟弟在這里嗎
Is your brother in the building?
我們可以呼叫他來
We can use the intercom.
不用了
No.
查爾斯  你想讓我們給誰打電話嗎
Charles...is there anyone you want us to call?
查克
Chuck.
Hey, Chuck.
查克  媽媽呢  怎么了
Chuck, where's Mom? What happened?
她去世了
She's gone.
什么  什么時候
What? W-when?
她怎么
How did...
她醒過嗎  她說什么了嗎
Did she wake up? Did she say anything?
沒有
No.
絕命律師
第二季 第十集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
翻譯  杏仁斯嘉麗  TheWalkingNerd   joy_bwl
翻譯  自然卷  克里斯  西陵折枝
校對  喃喃
打911
Call 911.
時間軸   夢龍  姜姜
快啊
Call 911!
歐尼  出去
Ernie, get out here!
后期  深山小新    總監  喃喃
你干什么
Hey, what the hell are you doin?!
明天再來
Come back tomorrow.
給你打五折
It'll be half the price.
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    美劇炸了
了解最新影視資訊字幕信息
需要救護車
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
-我這有紙巾  -好
- I got paper towels. - Good.
給我個墊子墊他的頭
Some for his head, gimme a cushion for his head!
等下  先別掛
Um, yeah, hold on. Hold on one second.
查克  振作點  振作點
Chuck. Come on. Come on.
查克
Chuck.
-查克  聽得見嗎  -復印中心
- Hey, Chuck, with us, buddy? - The copy center.
-查克  -金街615號
- Chuck. - 615 Gold.
哥們  你沒事吧
Buddy, y-you okay?
不  他臉色沒有發青
No, he doesn't look blue.
-我們這就送你去醫院  -蘭斯
- We're gonna get you to the hospital, okay? - ‭Lance.
-會沒事的  -我在這兒工作
- Everything will be all right. - I work here.
堅持一下  查爾斯  快到了
Hang tight, Charles. We're almost there.
小心
Watch yourself.
讓一讓
Coming through.
數三下  一二三
On 3. 1, 2, 3.
移床
Transferring.
查爾斯·麥吉爾  快六十歲了
This is Charles McGill, late 50s.
打印店雇員看見他在店內昏厥
He had a syncopal episode at a print shop, witnessed by an employee.
失去意識時間約一分鐘
Estimated loss of consciousness was one minute.
生命體征平穩
His vitals are stable.
前額有裂傷
He's got a laceration on his forehead
應該需要縫合
that appears to need suturing.
查爾斯  你感覺如何
Charles, how you doing tonight?
能跟我說話嗎
Can you talk to me?
有癥狀突然發作嗎
Seizure activity?
運送途中沒有  也沒有報告
Not in transfer and none reported.
無尿失禁
No urinary incontinence.
有家屬在場嗎
Do we have any family members?
-他弟弟在等候室  -好
- There's a brother in the waiting room. - Okay.
你給他打多少點滴了
How much fluid did you give him?
這還是第一公升
That's the first liter.
-燈  -你說什么  查爾斯
- Lights. - ‭What's that, Charles?
把燈關掉
Mnh, you have to turn off the lights.
-現在沒辦法關燈  親愛的  -天啊
-No, we can't do that right now, sweetie. - Ohh! God.
你撞傷了頭
You fell and hit your head.
我們得做一些檢查  好嗎
We're gonna need to do some tests, okay?
-不  不  -我們沒辦法...
- No. No. - ‭We can't --
我們需要開著燈才能幫你
We need the lights on to help you.
-不  -查爾斯  你能用力握我的手嗎
- No. - ‭Charles, can you squeeze my hand really hard?
把燈關...
Turn the lights...
那是什么
What is that?
檢查你的吸氧量而已  查爾斯
Okay, we're just checking your oxygen there, Charles.
-你有任何藥物過敏嗎  -沒有
- Do you have any allergies? - No.
目前是否在服用任何藥物
Are you on any medications?
沒有
Ohh, no.
好的  我現在要動一動你的手和腿
Okay. I'm gonna move your arms and legs,
覺得痛就告訴我  好嗎
and you tell me ‭if there's any pain, okay?
-有心電圖嗎  -什么
- Did we get an EKG? - The what?
各位  我們有心電圖嗎
Gentlemen, did we get an EKG?
-什么  -他現在接了五導聯
- What? - He's on a five-lead now.
還沒接十二導聯
We didn't get a 12-lead.
-不  -特莉莎  我們需要十二導聯
- No. - ‭Okay, Tricia, we're gonna need a 12-lead, please.
不要心電圖  不要心電圖
No EKG! No EKG!
查爾斯  我們必須做心電圖
Yes, Charles, ‭we need to do an EKG okay?
-不  你不懂  -查爾斯
- No, you don't understand. - Charles.
-我有特殊病癥  -查爾斯  我們要...
- I have a condition! - Charles, we need --
我有電磁過敏癥
I have a hypersensitivity to electricity!
-好  但你必須...  -查爾斯
- Okay, but you need... - Charles,
請你用雙腳抵住我的雙手
please push your feet against my hands.
-檢查你的頭部和頸部  -很好
- ...so we examine your head and your neck... - ‭Very good.
確認心臟沒問題  好嗎
...and make sure your heart's all right, okay?
拿開
Get these out of here.
-不  你不能碰這個  -我有一種病癥
- No, you can't touch this. - No, I-I-I have a condition.
-特莉莎  把燈打開  -你們沒經我同意
- Tricia, can I get a light? - I did not give you my consent.
-請別觸碰  -你們無權這么做
- You can't touch that. - You have no right to do this!
-我們得監測你的心率  -拿開
- We need to monitor your heart, okay? - Get these out of here!
-查爾斯  -放輕松
- Charles. - ‭Just relax.
-關燈  拜托  -放輕松
- The lights, please. - Just relax.
請你保持冷靜  查爾斯
Please stay calm, Charles.
查爾斯  你得配合我們
Charles, you need to cooperate with us.
這非常簡單的
This is gonna be very easy.
我們只需要抽一點點血
We're just gonna draw a little bit of blood,
縫合你的傷口  做個簡單的斷層掃描
suture up your wound, and do a very simple CAT scan.
-不  不能做掃描  -冷靜  冷靜
- No! No CAT scan! - Okay, c-calm, calm.
-不能做掃描  -特莉莎
- No CAT scan! - Tricia,
請將他固定
can we please get some restraints?
-你不明白  -男醫生麻煩進來
- You don't understand! - Gentlemen, please come in here.
求求你  把燈關掉
Please, turn off the lights.
要把他固定住
You have to hold him down, restrain him.
-請把燈關掉  -查爾斯
- Please turn off the lights! - Charles...
-這邊  -你得冷靜
- Right here. - ...we need you to calm down.
-你這是在謀殺我  -冷靜  查爾斯
- You're killing me! - Calm down, Charles.
-檢查了就沒事了  -你沒事的
- Just gonna get them and figure it out for you. - You're fine.
有我們在呢
We got you.
頭別抬起來
Just keep your head down.
他情況如何
How's he doing?
我也想告訴你
I'd love to be able to tell you,
但是不做檢查沒辦法確定
but we can't know for sure until we do those tests.
你知道我要說什么
You know what I'm gonna say.
你們為什么不能用傳統方法
Why can't you just go old-school -- you know,
檢查眼球  用聽診器之類的
look at his pupils, use a stethoscope -- that kinda thing?
他不想待在這里
He doesn't want to be here.
他想要什么和他需要什么
What he wants and what he needs
完全是兩碼事  吉米
are two very different things, Jimmy.
我們不知道他失去意識
We don't know if he lost consciousness
是心臟問題還是輕微中風引起的
because of a heart-related issue or if it was a mild stroke.
我們不知道他脊椎是否受傷
We don't know if his spine has been injured,
腦部是否腫脹
if his brain is swelling.
至少很有可能腦震蕩
He likely has a concussion, at least.
查克還是拒絕做檢查
Chuck is once again refusing these tests
因為會讓他受到"電磁轟炸"
because they involve being bombarded by electricity --
這是他的原話
his words.
跟他上次進醫院一模一樣
Nothing has changed since the last time he was in here.
我已經解釋得很清楚了
Look, I don't know ‭how to explain this any clearer.
我不會讓他住院的
I'm not committing him.
那申請臨時緊急監護人如何
What about a Temporary Emergency Guardianship?
他符合條件
I mean, he fits the parameters.
你跟我說他急需醫療
You're telling me he's in need of medical care so urgent
沒辦法等到法庭完成審核程序
that we can't wait around on court procedure.
沒錯
Most certainly.
而且查克無法理解后果
Yeah. And Chuck is not able to understand the consequences.
他是可以理解  但是他...
I mean, he can ‭understand them, but he --
沒錯
Absolutely.
法官也會這么理解的
A judge will see it that way, too.
之后我帶他回家就可以了
And then I take him home, and it's over.
等待檢驗結果和適當治療  可以
Pending results and proper treatment, yes.
我認識個法官  現在就可以聯系他
I know a judge we can call right now.
讓我來告訴他吧
Let me be the one to tell him.
老兄  你還好嗎
Hey, buddy. How's it going?
查克
Chuck.
你簡直是隨時待命
Well, if it isn't Johnny-on-the-spot.
什么意思
What? What does that mean?
歐內斯托在外面嗎
Is Ernesto out there?
對  你需要什么嗎
Yeah. Can I get you something?
歐內斯托
Ernesto!
麻煩你進來
Come in here, please!
放松
Look, just take it easy.
歐內斯托
Ernesto!
把你東西放那兒
Just put your stuff in there.
我把他叫來了
I got him.
你感覺怎么樣  麥吉爾先生
How are you feelin', Mr. McGill?
歐內斯托  我在那家復件店里
Ernesto, ‭how long was I unconscious
昏迷了多久
in that print shop?
我不確定
I'm not sure.
三十秒  一分鐘
30 seconds, a minute?
-還是兩分鐘  -大概有一分鐘吧
- 2 minutes? - ‭I'd say maybe about a minute.
你時而清醒時而迷糊
You were kinda in and out.
救護車來之前
And how long was I lying on the floor
我在地上躺了多久
before the ambulance arrived?
大概有十分鐘吧  我沒看表
About 10 minutes, I think, but I didn't look at the clock.
而那時你已經到了
And yet, you were there.
查克  我們能不能...
Chuck, can we, uh...
只有一種方法
There's only one way
能讓你那么快到達那里
you could have gotten there so quickly --
你根本沒走
you never left.
你太激動了
I think you're getting all wound up.
你得深呼吸...
Can you just take a few deep br--
你賄賂了他...
You bribed him --
-那個柜員  -什么
- that kid behind the counter. - What?
趁著歐內斯托離開而我還沒到
Between the time Ernesto left and I arrived,
你給了那個笨蛋錢
you paid that half-wit to swear
-讓他說他從沒見過你  -麥吉爾先生
- he'd never laid eyes on you. - Mr. McGill.
然后你就在附近一直看著
And then you stuck around to watch.
-為什么  想看我受苦嗎  -麥吉爾先生
- Why? Just wanted to see me suffer? - Mr. McGill.
想看我出洋相嗎
Just wanted to have a laugh at my expense?
我給他打了電話
I called him.
什么
What?
我在接你之前  給吉米打了電話
I called Jimmy earlier, before I picked you up.
他出現是因為我給他打了電話
He showed up when he did because I called him.
我很擔心你  所以...
I was worried about you, and I just --
我給他打了電話  對不起
I called him. I'm sorry.
出去  你們兩個都出去
Get out...both of you.
查克  有件事我必須得做
Chuck, there's something that I have to do,
真的很抱歉
and I'm really sorry --
真的非常抱歉
really, truly sorry,
但我必須做  為了你好
but I gotta do it, and it's for you.
你想讓我住院
You're trying to have me committed.
不  只是臨時...
No, it's a Temporary --
臨時緊急監護人
Temporary ‭Emergency Guardianship --
說法不同而已
to-may-to, to-mah-to.
你終于把我關起來了
Well, you've finally got me where you want me.
你看起來累壞了
Hey, you look beat.
回家休息吧
Why don't you go home and get some sleep?
我還撐得住
I'm fine to hang out, you know?
有什么需要盡管說
Whatever you need.
沒事  不用了
Nah. We're good here.
歐尼
Hey, Ernie.
你為什么說你給我打了電話
Uh, how come you said that about callin' me?
我也不知道
I don't know, man.
我本不想多嘴
Look, I didn't want to say anything,
但是你哥哥...
but your brother --
最近他說起你時的樣子...
the way he's been ‭talkin' about you lately --
就好像...他真的要收拾你  吉米
it's like...he's really out to get you, Jimmy.
我說不清
And...I don't know.
你是我的朋友
You're my friend.
謝謝
Thanks.
我明天給你電話
I'll call you tomorrow.
真懷念收發室
I miss the mailroom.
你們知道希波克拉底誓言嗎
Are you familiar with the Hippocratic oath?
你們應該知道
You should be.
歷史上最古老的具有約束力的文件之一
One of the oldest binding documents in history.
首先  不要傷害病人
Primum non nocere -- first, do no harm.
你們這樣對待我是不對的
This is not the way to treat my condition.
就好像  我對青霉素過敏
It's as though I had a -- an allergy to penicillin,
而你們卻非要用它來治療我的感染
and yet, you persist on treating my infection with it.
感謝你做類比  查爾斯
I appreciate the analogy, Charles,
但我覺得這個類比并不恰當
but I don't think it quite fits.
我們會在你不知不覺間
Look, we'll have you in and out of Radiology
就做完放射檢查的  好嗎
before you know it, all right?
然后我們會摘掉頸托
Then we can see about getting that neck collar off
讓你活動活動
and get you moving around.
好了  查爾斯  掃描就要開始了
Okay, Charles, the scan is starting now.
你躺著的臺子會移動
The table that you're on is going to move.
你會聽到一聲比較大的聲響
You're gonna hear a sound that might seem loud to you,
但是不用擔心
but it's nothing to worry about.
還沒消息呢
Still no word?
天啊
Jesus.
到底要花多久啊
How long is this gonna take?
她說整個檢查也就十分鐘而已
She said that whole test would be like 10 minutes.
也許他們得重做
Maybe they had to start over.
重做二十次嗎
What -- 20 times?
他應該回家
He should be home.
吉米  你這么做是對的
Jimmy, you're doin' the right thing.
你能把工作拿出來做嗎
Would you get your work out, please?
因為不知道還要在這等多久
Becouse God knows how much longer we're gonna be here.
如果你能做點別的我會感覺好點
I'd feel better ‭if you were doing something,
做點跟醫院無關的事
you know, unhospital-y.
跟醫院無關的
Unhospital-y.
好的
I'm on it.
我去問一下情況
You know what? I'm gonna go ask for an update.
好主意
Okay. Good idea.
你們是最偉大的一代
You are the greatest generation.
-吉米  -你們沒有挑起二戰
- Jimmy. ‭- You didn't start World War II,
但卻終結了它
but you sure as heck finished it.
如果這還不夠
And if that weren't enough,
你們還把九十多米高的火箭送上了月球
you sent a rocket 300 feet tall to the moon.
現在  你們到了遲暮之年
Now, in your golden years,
你們需要有人照顧
you need someone looking out for you,
需要一個可以信任的人
someone you can trust,
一個言必信  行必果的人
a man who says what he does and does what he says.
當你需要一個可靠的人
When you need someone to count on...
-我選吉米  -我選吉米
- Gimme Jimmy! - Gimme Jimmy!
我選吉米
Gimme Jimmy!
因為現在勇氣已經很少見了
Because moxie is in such short supply these days.
吉米·麥吉爾  你可以信賴的律師
Jimmy McGill -- A lawyer you can trust.
太棒了  吉米
It's really good, Jimmy.
你拍了一條很棒的廣告
You made a really good commercial.
謝了
Thanks.
吉米
Jimmy.
總算出來了  他怎么樣了
Oh, finally. So, how is he?
好消息是生理上無大礙
Well, the good news is that, physically, he's okay.
放射科醫生說查爾斯的
The radiologist said everything looks normal
頭和脊椎都很正常
with Charles' head and spine,
所以我們把他的頸圈卸了
so we took his neck collar off.
他頭部的傷會很快愈合
His head wound will heal just fine.
給他打了破傷風
We gave him a tetanus shot
因為他的接種記錄不是最新的
because his immunization records were not current.
你肯定不意外
I'm sure ‭that's no surprise to you.
那他心臟呢
And -- And -- And his heart?
很強健
Strong.
心電圖正常
The EKG was normal.
至于失去知覺  最可能的原因是
As far as losing consciousness, my best guess is
查爾斯的暈厥和壓力有關
Charles had what's called a stress-related syncope.
一般是恐慌癥發作
It's basically a panic attack,
但沒有中風和心臟問題
but no signs of a stroke or cardiac event.
但還是有...
However, there was...
并發癥
a complication.
查克  兄弟是我
Chuck? Hey, buddy, it's me.
醫生說一切正常  我們出院吧
They said everything looks good, so let's get you outta here.
你說呢
Whaddya say?
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
藥效應該已經過去了  對吧
Whatever you gave him should've worn off already, right?
我們觀察他幾個小時了
We watched him for several hours.
甚至都用了逆轉劑
We even gave him ‭what's called a reversal agent.
沒錯  鎮靜劑藥效過了
So, yes, the sedative wore off.
-是因為其他原因  -什么原因
- This is something else. ‭- What?
我們認為這是自誘導緊張癥
We think it's a state of self-induced catatonia.
"我們"  永遠是"我們認為"
"We" -- always with the "We."
我覺得就是你認為
I think it's you.
你是這屋子里唯一的醫生
You're the only doctor in the room.
我認為是你用機器燒壞了他的腦子
I think you fried his brain with that machine.
吉米
Jimmy.
-抱歉  真是扯淡  -吉米
- I'm sorry. This is bullshit. - Jimmy.
下一步會怎么樣
What next?
我第一次治療查爾斯時  他也是類似的狀態
When I first treated Charles, he was in a similar state.
你同意嗎
Wouldn't you agree?
我相信他清醒過來
I have to believe ‭that it's just a matter of time
只是時間問題
before he comes out of it.
時間問題
Matter of time.
好  那我就在這等著
Fine, then. I'll wait right here.
偏左  一點五角分
Shot left. 1.5 minutes.
這把槍能連射多少發
How many rounds've gone through the tube?
你說魯格762狙擊槍嗎
For a 762?
就算射掉3500發也沒啥影響
You can put 3,500 through it and never know.
關鍵是能射多快
It's about how tight she shoots.
這把槍速度飛快
And this one's tight as they come.
順射擊方向有風
I'd say there's a breeze picking up downrange.
槍管會變冷嗎
Your barrel gonna be cold?
希望如此吧
Let's suppose so.
那你開槍最好多留心
Well, then, you'd better have paid attention to that shot.
是啊
I'd better have.
向右調整  一點五角分
Adjusting right, 1.5 minutes.
開槍吧
Send it.
中了
Hit.
正中紅心
Center hit.
我建議你不要換子彈
I suggest you don't change up your ammo.
繼續用168格令船尾中空彈
Stick with the 168 grain boat-tail hollow point --
如果沒有障礙物  選它沒錯
if it's an open shot, that is.
如果你要射穿很厚的窗戶
Now, if you got to shoot through a heavy window,
我建議你換到180格令
I'll up you to a 180.
但你就得重新計算射擊參數了
But as you know, you'll have to recalculate the shot.
168就夠了
168'll do it.
多少盒
How many boxes?
就一盒
Just the one.
不用了  免費
No, it's on the house.
還有一件事
Uh, one last thing.
無意冒犯
No offense.
沒事
None taken.
吉米  可以給我點水嗎
Jimmy, can I get some water?
查克  你醒了
Chuck. Hey, buddy, you're back with us.
你怎么...
How you...
可以給我點水嗎
Can I get some water, please?
好好  我去拿
Yeah, yeah, water.
該死  抱歉
Oh, shit. Sorry. ‭
還要嗎
Want some more?
我記得最后一件事
Last thing I remember
就是他們把我送進那臺機器里
was that machine they put me in.
我昏迷多久了
How long was I out for?
有二十個小時了
Was...20 hours.
下一個任務就是把你帶出這鬼地方
And next order of business -- get you the hell outta here.
去哪
Where to next --
拉斯克魯塞斯的精神病院嗎
some insane asylum in Las Cruces?
一個你可以真正把我藏起來的地方嗎
Some place you can really tuck me away, but good?
回家  查克  你要回家
Home, Chuck. You're goin' home.
你心臟很好
Well, your heart's okay,
頭上的傷也沒事
and so is that crack on your head,
我想知道的就這些
so that's all I wanted to know.
臨時緊急監護人呢
What about the T.E.G.?
"T"不正是臨時的意思嗎
The "T" stands for "Temporary," Right?
你想上床嗎
You wanna go to bed?
不不  這更涼快
No, no. ‭It's -- It's cooler down here.
你還需要什么
What can I get you?
我給你泡點茶  好茶葉
I'll make you some tea -- uh, the good stuff,
不是醫院里那種發黃的水
not that brown water they have at the hospital.
不用了
I'm fine.
我去給你泡茶
I'll make you some tea.
吉米  別去
Jimmy. No.
你就...
Just --
你已經完成任務了
You've done your duty.
你可以走了
You can go now.
我有點咄咄逼人了
That came out a bit harsh.
我在醫院時已經被百般折磨了
Look, I've been zapped and poked and prodded,
現在  我只想自己待會
and now I just I wanna be left alone.
如果你身體又出什么問題
If things start going south for you again,
我怎么能知道呢
how am I even gonna know?
我沒事的  我保證
I'm fine. I promise.
看見沒
See?
已經感覺好多了
Feeling better already.
我連鑰匙都沒有
I mean, ‭I don't even have a key, so...
我能叫歐尼回來嗎
Can I get Ernie back here?
至少讓我為你做這件事  行嗎
Would you let me ‭do that for you, at least?
你需要有人來照看你
You need someone lookin' in on ya.
你得吃飯  不是嗎
You gotta eat, right?
好吧
All right.
早日康復  查克
Feel better, Chuck.
別這么做
好的  我這就去辦
All right, I will get right on that.
下周應該就能幫你辦好
I should have it for you by early next week.
祝你今日愉快  柯林斯先生
You have yourself ‭a wonderful day, Mr. Collins.
對了
Oh! There you go.
把墨鏡拿出來
Yeah, get the sunglasses out.
外面很亮
It's very bright.
得保護好眼睛
Gotta protect the ol' peepers.
你得...
You gotta...
好  帥呆了
Yep, looking sharp.
就這樣
Bingo.
回頭見
Uh, bye-bye, now.
好了
Okay.
大家好  抱歉讓你們久等
Folks, I'm sorry about the wait,
我為每位委托人花這么長時間
but the attention I give each client means
意味著有時候大家需要等等
sometimes, things get a little...backed up.
不過我向你們保證
Uh but I promise
會按順序為你們服務
to get to each and every one of you in turn.
德謝佐女士  親愛的  你是下一位
Mrs. DeShazo, my dear, I believe you're next.
先問一句  有誰想喝咖啡嗎
But first, may I get anybody some coffee?
我能和你談談嗎
Can I talk to you?
稍等一下
Uh, excuse me one second.
我們昨天就得找個前臺了
We have got to get a receptionist -- like, yesterday.
吉米  霍華德剛才來電話了
Jimmy, Howard just called.
他說他一早上都在聯系你
He says he's been trying to reach you all morning.
那又怎樣  叫他別煩你了  給我留言
So? Tell him to stop bothering you and leave me a message.
是查克的事
It's about Chuck.
他只說很重要
It's impmptant -- that's all he'll say.
好吧
Okay.
很遺憾  我的同事告訴我
Unfortunately, uh, my associate tells me
我有簡短但緊急的法律事務要處理
I'm needed for some brief but pressing legal business.
我很快打個電話就好
I just need to make one quick phone call.
誰想要咖啡來著
Uh, in the meantime, who was it who wanted coffee?
好的  這位年輕的女士會給你們倒咖啡
Yeah, okay, uh, this young lady will get you coffee...
還有面包圈  如果還有的話
and, also, doughnuts if there are any left.
我要咖啡  不加奶
I want coffee, but I do not want cream.
朱莉  是我  給霍華德回電話
Hey, Julie, it's me, returning Howard's call.
對
Yeah.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
吉米  我就問一個問題
Jimmy, ‭I have just one question --
這是你策劃的嗎
are you behind this?
策劃什么
Am I behind what?
吉米  我現在正忙著呢
Jimmy, I'm kind of in the middle of somethin' right now.
-過會再來吧  -不  不  不
- Come back later. - No, no, no.
拜托  把門打開
Come on. Open the door.
我知道你為什么來  我們可以一會再說
I know why you're here. We can discuss it later.
我正忙著呢  再見
Right now I'm busy, goodbye.
滿意了吧
You happy now?
這樣不行  我連這里的鑰匙都沒有
It's not right -- me not havin' a key to this place.
查克
Chuck?
查克  這怎么回事
So, Chuck...uh, what's up?
你弄了個...
You got a little, uh --
你弄了個工程啊
You got a little, uh, uh, project goin' on?
你想跟我說說這是怎么回事嗎
Uh, something you maybe wanna tell me about?
查克  跟我說說行嗎
Whaddya say, Chuck? Y-- Uh, clue me in?
這些墻是石膏和板條的
These walls are plaster and lath --
對無線電波完全沒防護作用
completely invisible to the radio spectrum.
一點也沒有
No protection at all --
我還不如直接站到一片牧草地里呢
I might as well be standing in the middle of a pasture.
真不知道當初自己怎么想的
I don't know what I was thinking.
一開始就該這樣
Shoulda done this from the start.
你是說這么做  用...
What, you shoulda done this, with the, uh --
我覺得這些墻還挺結實的
See, I think these walls are pretty solid. I think --
一種金屬材質外殼  能阻止電磁波進入
我需要的是一個法拉第籠
See, what I really need is a proper Faraday cage.
那才是我需要的
That's what I need.
我們該坐下來  休息一會  伙計
I think we need to sit down, take a break, buddy.
求你了
Please?
別跟我來這一套  吉米
Do not patronize me, Jimmy.
我沒瘋  好嗎
I'm not crazy, all right?
我從沒說你瘋了
‭I-I never said you were crazy.
你可能只是累壞了
That -- You're probably exhausted,
情有可原
a-and justifiably.
聽著
Hey, come on. Hey.
就五分鐘  然后你接著忙你的
Five minutes, and then right back at it.
我沒事
I'm fine.
來吧  查克
Come on, Chuck.
休息一會
Just a break.
-小心點  -我知道
- Careful. - ‭I know.
霍華德說你辭職了
Howard tells me you quit HHM.
我沒有辭職
I didn't quit.
我退休了
I retired.
聽起來可不像這么回事
That's not what it sounded like.
不管怎樣  這太突然了  你不覺得嗎
Regardless, it's kinda outta the blue, don't you think?
他很擔心你
He's worried about you.
他該松了一口氣才對
He should be relieved.
松了一口氣  怎么會
Relieved? Why would he be relieved?
你可是他的頂梁柱
You're his Number One Guy.
沒了你  律所肯定每況愈下
Without you, that whole place goes down the drain.
所以  你退休了
So, you -- you retired --
不僅從哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所退休
not just from HHM,
也退出律師界了嗎
but the law?
這可不好  查克
That's not good, Chuck.
律師界  需要你
The -- The law... needs you.
別說了
Just stop it.
你也需要它
And you need it.
到底是為什么  查克
What brought this on exactly, Chuck?
你不做律師還能做什么
'Cause I don't know what you are if you're not a lawyer.
你還沒讓我被取消律師資格
How are you gonna retire before you get me disbarred,
還沒把我趕出城  怎么能退休
before you run me outta town on a rail, huh?
以后可就我一個麥吉爾在律師界混了
I'll be the only McGill carrying the family name.
你怎么忍得了
You can't have that.
是因為  你沒能挽回梅薩維德銀行嗎
Is this... ‭'cause you lost Mesa Verde?
那又怎樣  誰會在意
So what? Who cares?
而且  如果你真的覺得
And, hey, if you truly do think
這事是我在背后捅你刀子
that I rat-fucked you on that thing --
當然我并沒有  不過隨便了
which I did not, but whatever --
你知道嗎
well, you know what?
你應該生氣  應該報復
You get mad! Take action!
別躲在你這法拉第什么
Don't just hide out in your -- your Faraday whatever --
破籠子里
your cage thing here.
不  你該永遠不退休才對
No! You -- No retirement for you!
等你九十九歲了
When you're 99,
還要對著機器人法官做結辯陳詞  然后倒地身亡
you can drop dead giving closing arguments to JudgeBot 3000 --
對了  那東西也是用電的
which will run on electricity, by the way.
這才是你的未來好嗎
That's your future, okay?
-所以  -我
- So... ‭ - I...
我做不了這個工作了
‭I can't do the job anymore.
什么意思  你怎么就干不了了
What do you mean? ‭'Course you can do the job.
我犯了一個錯誤
I made a mistake.
什么錯誤
What mistake?
一個很小的錯誤  把銀行地址搞錯了
A simple, ‭nothing little bank address --
1261號寫成了1216號
1216 instead of 1261.
我搞砸了
I screwed it up!
我讓委托人蒙受損失
I hurt the client.
徹徹底底搞砸了
Blew it completely and utterly.
而且我還把這怪到你頭上
And then I blamed -- And then I blamed you.
都怪這該死的電流
It's this goddamned electricity!
一點一點消磨我  把我的機能消磨殆盡
It's wearing me down! It's wearing down my faculties!
我的頭腦  我的思維  它曾經
My brain...my mind -- it used to be --
它曾經那么敏捷
You know, it used to work!
可現在完全不管用了
And now it doesn't anymore.
有人因為我而受傷害
People got hurt because of me.
是時候結束了
Time to end it.
如果我告訴你你并沒有犯錯呢
What if I told you ‭you didn't make a mistake?
天哪  吉米  別來安慰我了
For Christ's sakes, Jimmy, stop humoring me.
別說得好像一切都不是我的錯
Stop trying to talk everything right.
我背叛了你
I rat-fucked you.
是我干的
It was me.
尼克松都得為我自豪
I would made Nixon proud.
我把1261改成了1216
I changed 1261 to 1216.
是我干的
It was me.
事情的經過就像你說的一樣
It all went down exactly like you said --
分毫不差
I mean, exactly.
我篡改了文件
I doctored the copies.
買通打印店的小伙子讓他為我撒謊
I paid the kid at the shop to lie for me.
每一個細節都如你所料  你太神了
It is insane how you got every detail exactly right.
這下你能放心了吧
So you can relax, okay?
你的腦子好用著呢  馬力十足
'Cause that brain of yours is chugging along at 1,000% efficiency.
你說的是真的嗎
Are you telling the truth,
還是你只是為了讓我好受點
or are you just trying to make me feel better?
當然是為了讓你好受點
I am sayin' it to make ya feel better.
不然我怎么可能說出來
I sure as shit wouldn't be telling ya otherwise.
但是  沒錯  這就是真的
But, yes... it's the truth.
你這么大費周章就為了羞辱我嗎
You'd go to such lengths to humiliate me?
我是為了金
I did it for Kim!
她廢寢忘食地拿下梅薩維德銀行
What -- She worked her butt off to get Mesa Verde
而你和霍華德就喝喝威士忌坐享其成
while you and Howard sat around sipping Scotch and chortling.
什么哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill --
狄更斯小說中的守財奴
應該叫斯克魯奇馬利律所才對
more like Scrooge and Marley!
梅薩維德銀行是金的
Kim deserves Mesa Verde --
不是你  也不是哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所的
not you, not HHM.
她爭取來的  她需要它
She earned it, and she needs it!
我這么做是為了幫她
I did it to help her,
但我真不知道這會給你帶來那么大的傷害
but I-I honestly didn't think it would hurt you so bad.
我以為你只會說  "靠  我犯了個錯誤"
I thought you'd just say, "Oh, crap, I made a mistake,"
然后繼續過你的日子  這才是正常人會干的
and go on with your life, like a normal person!
可你偏不
But, oh, no!
是我打錯了如意算盤
Wishful thinking!
所以  我能不能告訴霍華德
So, can I, uh, tell Howard
你不辭職也不退休了
you're not quitting or retiring or whatever?
還有  能不能把這些破玩意從墻上弄下來
And can we take all this shit down off the walls?
我這就打電話給霍華德
I'm gonna go call Howard.
吉米
Jimmy.
你剛剛承認犯了一項重罪你知道吧
You do realize ‭you just confessed to a felony?
算是吧
I guess.
可你覺得好多了  是吧
But you feel better, right?
再說了  就我們倆  空口無憑
Besides, ‭it's your word against mine.
各大應用市場均可下載
人人美劇APP看美劇就來人人美劇
更新快 無刪減
最大最全的美劇平臺
掃碼即刻下載